Chairman Xu, I’ve made it very clear to you
Forced feelings
Not suitable
I just want to treat Rumeng as my own sister now
Fine then
You all
Just let it happen naturally
Since you did the company a big favor this time
I won’t make it hard for you
But
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
You have to promise me
One more thing
What other thing?
Do the internet project properly
And also
You still have to be my godson
Not be a godson
What’s the reason for that?
You didn’t give me a reason to make you my son-in-law
No
These are two separate things
One thing
You still won’t call me
Godfather
Hey
Hello, President Zheng
Looks like you’ve already adapted well
It’s okay
What’s this?
This is the project’s introduction material
There are some documents that need your signature
Okay
Leave it here
You need to pick up the pace
This is just a small portion from before
Later,
Other departments will coordinate with you one by one
There is much more to be processed later
It feels different from what I imagined
Looks like this overbearing CEO
is not that easy to be
Brother-in-law
You can’t back out
So many people throughout the company
are all counting on you
Got it
Oh, right
From now on,
I need to change how I address you
You and my sister don’t have that relationship now
Calling you brother-in-law seems not quite right
That’s not right
Not appropriate
President Zheng
No, that’s too formal
Fengfeng
Mm
A bit cheesy
Brother Nanfeng
Just call me Nan Feng
Nan Feng
Come on, come on, time to eat
So lavish!
I added extra for you
I cooked it myself
Youyou
You’re busy with your own work too
You...
I feel bad
I’m happy to
Go ahead and eat
I just don’t want you overworked
It’s not hard
Go ahead and eat
I’ll come back in a bit
Looks like this won’t work
I just sent off Xu Rumeng
And now Xu Youyou shows up
These two sisters are set on making me miserable
Sir, you can’t go in, you can’t go in
Let me in
I want to see Brother Nanfeng
Do you know my relationship with Brother Nanfeng?
No matter the relationship, you still can’t go in
Let me in
Brother Nanfeng
A Qiang
I finally found you
How did you let yourself get like this
I’ve been in Shengang for over a week
And I didn’t have your contact info
So I asked around everywhere
If I couldn’t find you, I couldn’t go on
Uh...
Can I have a bite first
Eat
Get him a new pair of chopsticks
Eat slowly, don’t choke
Here, have some water
Nan Feng, A Qiang
You two eat first
I’ll go handle something
How did you let yourself get like this
I haven’t eaten for three days
I swam here from Haicheng
The little money I had ran out long ago
You were doing fine in Haicheng
Why did you come to Shengang
Boss Cheng kicked me out
What happened
He’s arrogant and overbearing at the company
And he’s narrow-minded
He’s harsh to the old brothers too
I talked back to him a couple of times
Then he told me to get lost
What about Zhiyi
Sister Zhiyi
She hardly goes out now
I think she has a lot on her mind
Seems she doesn’t like to talk much anymore
That Cheng guy hasn’t made things hard for her, right
Mm, no
What about A Ming
A Ming
He still remembers the old ties
He doesn’t want to leave
I figured it’s good if he doesn’t leave
He can look after Sister Zhiyi a bit
True
Brother Nanfeng
You’ve made it in Shengang
Just starting out
So-so
Then can I stay here
Keep following you
Sure, sure
Just think of it like Haicheng
I can’t just freeload meals, can I
Maybe you could see about giving me
some kind of job
I do have something
It’s just a bit troublesome
It depends on whether you can do it
I’ll go through blades and fire, Brother Nanfeng
Come here, come here
Will this work
I think it will
I’m not sure
I’ll back you up
I love you
I fancy you
I really love you
Hey, stop right there
I’ve been really super frustrated lately
You’re in my head every day
Round and round and round
I think about you all day long
I really can’t take it anymore
Will you date me
Please, just give me a chance
I promise you’ll fall in love with me
Will you do me a favor
Let’s watch a movie together
Titanic
You jump, I jump
I don’t care anymore, I don’t care
This is just how I am
What are you doing, A Qiang?
Nothing.
Then why are you sneaking around
at my office door?
I...
Stop right there.
I need to talk to you.
Go ahead.
Well...
What is it?
Why are you hemming and hawing?
That's not like you.
I have things to do.
Spit it out.
Uh, uh...
The cinema next door has a buy-one-get-one deal.
I happen to have two tickets.
I want to give you one.
A movie ticket.
Ah.
Titanic
Um...
I heard it's a pretty good love story.
A love story.
How come I heard it's a disaster film?
A disaster film?
You can't even tell a love story from a disaster film.
Find someone else.
Hey.
A disaster film?
Isn't it a love story?
How did it go?
She said I can't even tell a love story
from a disaster film.
and just turned me down.
Keep trying.
What else can I do?
Just watching a movie is too dull.
You need to use some tactics.
What tactics?
I miss you.
Whenever dusk falls,
the evening breeze blows.
I miss you.
the riddle of life
try not to see it too clearly.
Close your eyes.
Don't answer.
The evening breeze blows and blows
Go with the wind.
Tonight, children, don't cry in secret.
Don't cry in secret.
The evening breeze blows and blows
Go with the wind.
As night falls with the stars,
fall gently asleep.
Feel the evening breeze.